{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "When you are working with a Sitecore.Data.Items.Item object, which method should you use to get a list of all its children?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": ".GetChildren()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Axes.GetChild()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Axes.GetDescendants()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Database.GetChildren()"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "The GetChildren() method returns a list of an item's children in the form of a ChildList collection."
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is a Sitecore item?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "A page the visitor views on the website"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "An entity storing the information used to find the content in the file system"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "The construct Sitecore uses to store data"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "A definition for the type of date that you want to store"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "A Sitecore item is what Sitecore uses to store data."
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "When you patch in changes to the Sitecore.config file, how can you control the order in which your changes are applied?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "In App_Config/, create <order> entries in the Sitecore.Patch.config file"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "In App_Config/Include, use a naming convention and sub-folders for config files"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "In App_Config/Include/Project, add your config files"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "In Web.Config, manually insert the changes in order"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Recommended practice is to use the App_Config/Include folder, where folders and files are loaded alphabetically."
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Select the name of the Sitecore component-based architecture guidelines from the list.",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Habitat"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Adaptive"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Bootstrap"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Helix"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Helix is a set of overall design principles and conventions for Sitecore development.Throughout the Helix documentation you will find various examples from Habitat."
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Select the name of the Sitecore component-based architecture guidelines from the list.",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "/App_Config/Include/z.config"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "/App_Config/Include/b/b.config"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "/App_Config/Include/b/c.config"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "/App_Config/Include/c/a.config"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Config files are read in alphabetical order and it overrides settings from the previous one."
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What happens if the same field name is used in two separate inherited data templates?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "The field will be merged into one."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "The field will be duplicated."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Throws a duplicate field error."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "It will rename the second filed with index."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "The field name will be duplicated. This is not recommended practice."
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What field type can I use with Rendering Parameters?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Simple field types (e.g. Text, Link, Date) and list types (e.g. Droplist, Multilist, Checklist)"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "All field types"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "All field types except custom fields"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Only custom field types"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Rendering parameters can use all field types."
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What does it do when you make an item bucketable?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Become retrievable by using the Sitecore Search engine."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Children of the item can be bulk-edited."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "The item can be only used as a folder."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "The item is hidden."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Bucketable is the ability of an item or template to be stored or hidden in buckets or Item Buckets. All the Sitecore items are retrievable by the Sitecore search engine."
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How can I open a bucketable item?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use the Sitecore search functionality to locate and open the item."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Right click the item and select Open."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Select view item option."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use Sitecore Bucket API command."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "If you want to open a bucketable item that is placed in an item bucket, you must click the item bucket and use the Sitecore search functionality to locate and open the item."
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "When I made Template bucketable, the existing items are still not hidden. What should I do?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use Sitecore Bucket API command, Bucket-item."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Sync the existing items."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Enable item bucketable options in Template config."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use Template Manager and update Bucketable Settings in the Configure tab."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Once you sync the items, new items based on that template automatically work as buckets without any further action."
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How does Sitecore support one of the CMS pillars, Presentation?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Layouts and components"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Items"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Experience Editor"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Data definition: Templates, Content: Items, Presentation: layouts and components."
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What should you define in a template?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Fields, Field Sections, Icons and Base Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Fields, Field Sections, Icons and Standard Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Fields, Field Sections, Favicons and Template Name"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Template Name, Fields, Field Sections, Display Icon"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "We definitely need fields, field sections and base template. Icon is highly recommended practice."
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Which field type do I use to store formatted html",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Rich text field"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "HTML field"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "HTML Format field"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Raw HTML field"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "Rich text field can be used to store formatted html."
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is the name of the template all templates should inherit from?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Base Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Parent Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Standard Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "The Templates"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "It is called Standart Templates. It is a good idea to create _Base Template from Standard Template and inherit from it for extensibility."
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Where do you define default and initial values?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Standard Values"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Base Templates"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Init Values"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Rendering Parameters"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "Standard Values can define default and initial values."
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Where should I set insert options as a best practice?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Standard Values"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Content Item"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Template for the item"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Rendering configuration option"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "In the Standard Values, so they are applied as a default to newly created items."
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How can I use placeholders inside of placeholders?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use dynamic placeholder."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Add allowed control to the placeholder."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Add placeholder in the Placeholder Settings."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "This cannot be done directly."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Cannot do it directly. You can use components inside of placeholders that define other placeholders"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What do you need to do to allow users to add and remove components from a placeholder using the Experience Editor?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use dynamic placeholder."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Create a Placeholder setting item for that placeholder."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Make the user Admin."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use Content Manager to make Component editable."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Creating a Placeholder setting item for that placeholder will allow users to edit components."
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How to fix Layout not found error page?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Create a Placeholder setting item for the layout."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Define layout in the presentation details."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Add the appropriate View in the component settings"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Correct the path for .cshtml file in the component settings."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "You will get this error when you request a page that has no layout defined in the presentation detail."
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What tools can I use to install Sitecore?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Manual or zip file, EXE, Scripts"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "EXE"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Sitecore Rocks and SIM"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Manual or zip file, Scripts, Sitecore Rocks, SIM, EXE"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Sitecore can be installed by the following methods: Manual or sip file, Scripts, Sitecore Rocks, SIM, EXE."
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Where can Presentation Details be set?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Experience Editor (Design Mode), Content Editor, Template Manager, Sitecore Rocks"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Text Editor (Design Mode), Content Editor, Template Manager, Sitecore Rocks"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Document Editor (Design Mode), Content Editor, Template Manager, Sitecore Rocks"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "None of the above"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "Presentation detailed can be set by Experience Editor (Design Mode), Content Editor, Template Manager, Sitecore Rocks."
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What are the 3 folders in the physical path of the content folder that hosts the Sitecore application?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Website, data, text file"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Website and data"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Text file, data and ERM"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Website, data, and database"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Sitecore application requires Website, Data, Database folders."
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What are the SIM installation features?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Install any version of Sitecore from a repository of installers, Install modules and packages, Reinstall the same configuration."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Install any version of Sitecore from a repository of installers, Install modules and packages, Create a new configuration."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Install any version of Sitecore from a repository of installers, Install modules and packages, Reinstall a different configuration."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "None of the above"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What are the SIM Import/Export features?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Import an entire set of Sitecore databases with content and export to a new environment."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Export an entire set of Sitecore database with content and import to a new environment."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Export an three Sitecore databases with content and import to a new environment."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "None of the above"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Where is the license located?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Sitecore application root folder/Data/licenses/license.xml"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Sitecore application root folder/Website/App_Config/license.xml"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Sitecore application root folder/Data/license.xml"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "None of the above"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "The default path for license is: wwwroot/website name/Data/license.xml"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Where does Master database publish items to?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "xDB"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "The Web database"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "The Core database"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "The Master database"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": "Items are published to the Web database from the Master database."
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Publishing synchronizes what between master and web databases?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Updating new items, updating edited items, updating deleted or unpublishable items."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Updating new items, updating edited items, removing deleted or unpublishable items."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Adding new items, updating edited items, removing deleted or unpublishable items."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Updating new items, updating edited items, removing deleted or unpublishable items, updating index"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "It does not update index. Note that deleted or unpublishable items are removed by publishing."
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What are the types of publishing?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Delayed, Linear, and Dedicated"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Parallel, Linear, and Dedicated"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Delayed, Parallel, and Dedicated"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Synchronised, Delayed, Parallel and Dedicated"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "Exam tip: make sure to understand the difference between delayed, parallel and dedicated publishing types."
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Which of the following are the foundation pillars of a Web Content Management System?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Data Definition, Content, Presentation"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Data Definition, Content, Workflow"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Content, Workflow, Presentation"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Wordpress, Sitecore, Drupal"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "Data definition: Templates, Content: Items, Presentation: layouts and components."
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is a General Link field used for?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "To save the URL to use to render a particular item."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "To store a link to a presentation component."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "To store the contents of an anchor tag."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "To keep a reference to one or more items in the tree."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "Exam tip: Make sure to understand what General Link field does."
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "To take advantage of Sitecore's integrated marketing & analytics capabilities, what do you need to implement?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Experience Analytics"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Experience Automation"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Sitecore Marketing Cloud"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Experience Database"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How can you handle more than one input form on a controller rendering in Sitecore?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Cannot handle more than one form unless using View Renderings."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Use Sitecore.Ajax.GetFormData()."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Create an extension method invoking the FormHandler() and Use Ajax.BeginForm() and specify the controller and action."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Only Use Ajax.BeginForm() and specify the controller and action."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Why would you create the Visual Studio outside the webroot?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "The solution becomes more portable."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "It is required if you want to use source control."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Builds are faster outside the webroot."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "It eliminates the need to deploy code changes."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is the purpose of a Field Editor?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "To enable edition in the Experience Editor."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "To allow editors to change the field type."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "To open the Rich text editor for a field."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "To opens a pop up where fields are edited."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Which of the following are reasons for using field types in Sitecore?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "To define the raw value stored in the database, to determine which editor control will be used in the authoring tools, to determine the API field class used in code."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "To define the raw value stored in the database, to determine which editor control will be used in the authoring tools, to determine EXE class used in code."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "To define the default value stored in the database, to determine which editor control will be used in the authoring tools, to determine the API field class used in code."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "To define the default value stored in the database, to determine which values will be used in the authoring tools, to determine the API field class used in code."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is Sitecore's easy-to-use authoring tool and what functionality does it provide?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "The Development Editor provides editing and designing functionality."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "The Experience Editor provides editing and designing functionality."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "The Content Editor provides editing and designing functionality."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "The Experience Editor provides editing and database import/export functionality."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Which interface would an author use to see and edit items in a tree structure?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "The Development Editor"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "The Experience Editor"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "The Content Editor"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "The Experiment Editor"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What does an unversioned field contain?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Data for all versions in all languages"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "One version of the data per language"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "The latest version of the data"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "The latest published version of the data"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "A shared field contains a single version of the data for all versions in all languages. An unversioned field contains one version of the data per language."
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "When would you use the DisableWebEdit parameter when rendering a field?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "When the field has a default value."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "When the field is rendered from the rendering model."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "When rendering a field inside the <title> tag in the <head> of HTML"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "When rendering an image field"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How do I display the content of a field in code?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "@Html.Sitecore().Field(<field name>)"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "@Html.Sitecore().Parameter(<field name>)"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "@Html.Sitecore().Raw(<field name>)"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "@Html.Sitecore().GetItem(<field name>)"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What can I use to translate fields and help texts in the Sitecore client?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Sitecore Dictionary entries"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Sitecore Multilingual Function"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Unversioned field"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Sitecore rocks"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "When would you set languageEmbedding option to never?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Never set languageEmbedding option to never"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "The site is not multilingual"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Always set languageEmbedding option for security"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Sitecore doesn't have languageEmbedding option."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How would you display the direct children of the Home item?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use Sitecore.Context.Site.StartPath and invoke GetChildren()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Use Sitecore.Context.Site.HomePath and invoke GetChildren()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Use GetChildren(<path to home>)"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use GetChildren(<item id of home>)"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": "Sitecore.Context.Site.StartPath retrieves the Home item. GetChildren() will retrieve the direct children of the Home items."
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is the preferred way to modify the web.config",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Add web.config in the visual studio project, update it and publish"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Use .config file in App_Config/Include"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Use Sitecore Rocks configuration manager"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use Sitecore admin configuration manager"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Config changes get added alphabetically by default. How can I change it?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use <loadOrder>"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Cannot be changed"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Use Sitecore Rocks configuration manager"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use Sitecore admin configuration manager"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is the CMS parts of Sitecore?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Sitecore Experience"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "xManagement"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "xDB"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Sitecore Marketing"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What item setting needs to be specified for authors to be able to add content?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Standard Values"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Insert Options"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Allowed Renderings"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Content Insert Options"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What do you need to create to enable Dynamic Binding?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Standard Values"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Insert Options"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Allowed Renderings"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Placeholder"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A4",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What parts of the page are typically added using Static Binding?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "View Rendering items"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Scaffolding, like headers and footers"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Static content such as Images"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "<title> in <header>"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "It is a best practice to avoid static binding even for header and footer as the requirements may change to make them editable."
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What part of presentation details applies to all versions of an item?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Final Layout"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Shared Layout"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Standard Layout"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Rendering Layout"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Shared Layout is stored in _Renderings of presentation details while final layout is in _Final Renderings."
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Why would you use dynamic placeholders",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "To reuse a component containing placeholders."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "To reuse a component not containing placeholders."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "To reuse a component with static binding."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "To reuse a component with dynamic binding."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What does the item Resolver do?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Maps a URL to an item in the content tree."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Generate URL based on the site configuration."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Retrieves an URL of an item."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Update items when published from Master to Web."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How would you retrieve the URL of an item?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use LinkManager.GetItem()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Use LinkManager.GetItemUrl()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Use LinkManager.GetUrl()"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use LinkManager.GetItemPath()"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "To retrieve items: Item item = Sitecore.Context.Item; var url = Sitecore.Links.LinkManager.GetItemUrl(item);"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Which search providers does Sitecore ship with by default?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Solr and Elastic Search"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Solr and Azure Search"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Solar and Azure Search"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Only Solr"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "Sitecore 9.0 and above ships with Azure Search in addition to Solr."
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What happens when an item inside a bucket is not bucketable?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Cannot create an item."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Item is not hidden."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Become bucketable item and hidden."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Pop up option to make the item bucketable appears."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A2",
      "feedback": "The item is not hidden. It appears as a normal child item"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Which method is not supported by Sitecore's implementation of IQueryable<T>?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "GetResults"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Sort"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "GroupBy"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Slice"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "Methods such as GroupBy, Aggregate and Sum are not supported"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What happens if a role denies an access right and another one allows it?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Allowed"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Results in error"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Denied"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Sitecore does not allow this scenario to happen"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "Deny always takes priority."
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "Where can I check the effective permission of an account?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Access viewer"
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Identity and access manager"
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Access manager"
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Sitecore Rocks"
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What happens if an item version is not in a final workflow state?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "No automatic versioning and version is not publishable."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Automatic versioning but version is not publishable."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Publishable without versioning."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Content author cannot edit the content through Experience Editor."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "How can you make it easier to communicate issues with Sitecore Support?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Use the Support Package Generator from the Sitecore Marketplace."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Provide the phone number."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "Zip the App_Data folder and attached to the Support ticket."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Use Sitecore Rocks."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A1",
      "feedback": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "answerType": "radio",
      "question": "What is the best way to source control Sitecore items?",
      "answerOptions": [
        {
          "id": "A1",
          "option": "Export as a zip file and add to the repo."
        },
        {
          "id": "A2",
          "option": "Use Sitecore Rocks."
        },
        {
          "id": "A3",
          "option": "By Serialising them."
        },
        {
          "id": "A4",
          "option": "Take SQL Server snapshot after deployment."
        }
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A3",
      "feedback": "You can use tools like TDS or Unicorn to serialise items and source control them."
    }
  ]
}
